i recorded this and my kid jumped on the
bed and the camera fell over so i'm
recording it
you asked for feedback on your
presentation yesterday and i want to
give it to you but i'm not going to use
your name because i'm going to release
this so that
anyone who's meant to see it will see it
so first of all
i just want to say that you're an
amazing woman up to amazing things in
the world
and i want all the best for you you are
here to do powerful things this is a
hard place to be doing it this is like
the world is not set up to amplify our
message
and help us make a living wage in our
saving the world projects
i get it it sucks and mlm
is not the answer that being said your
presentation
was wonderful you were very eloquent you
did a very good job
you sounded like you knew what you were
talking about and you sold essential
oils
the problem was you did not know what
you were talking about
it was full of broken science and broken
broken things
essential oils are not a hand sanitizer
please don't tell that to people during
a pandemic you are going to kill
people people i love people that are me
you're going to kill
essential oils are powerful
but doterra is not there to help people
with their health they're there to make
a profit
they're there to have you sell 150 a
month and
have your whole downline do it so they
need you to ingest
in whatever way possible 150 worth of
essential oils you'll buy it the next
month in the next month
if you were just doing that aromatherapy
wise you can't go through that much
nobody needs 150 of essential oils a
month
even if you were knowledgeable and even
if there was nothing broken in that
science in that presentation
how you get people there was was
unethical it's sketchy to be like i'm
having a health and wellness thing
and not telling people what you're doing
and then they sign up for and then i
feel bad you send me a 20
package the fact it costs basically 20
to send me that package and yes i get
with people in the states it's going to
be cheaper that's a lot of investment
for someone to show up who
on your side to have somebody show up
who
is not in it at all for the essential
oils or the mlm
knowing that people aren't going to show
up if people know it's an mlm they're
not going to show up
they shouldn't show up you would never
do that for your other project
to say like oh just trick people into
coming and then like by the way a
resource-based economy
because it wouldn't work it's not going
to get the right people there
that there's no barriers to entry anyone
can get involved in this
anyone can become an essential oil sales
person means you don't
have to be an expert in it and you can
lie through your teeth and make everyone
else look bad even who is in it for good
reasons
that you need to have a story about
chronic illness that got made better
and then you have to believe it so you
can sell it to yourself and everybody
else
as somebody with a chronic illness i'm
sure you know how annoying it is
for people who find the magic bullet to
then think it's the magic bullet for
everybody else
i'm glad that you found something that
helped you it doesn't mean it's going to
help the next person and the next person
and even if it does doterra is not the
way to get it
100 like they manufacture that you need
to make it at 100
you need to get these people paying 150
they need to get you to ingest that much
that is not the same level as what would
be the healthiest for you
again i use essential oils lemons what
helps with my nausea
it's a life it's a lifesaver it didn't
get rid of my nausea i didn't cure my
brain tumors it didn't
they are awesome doterra is not the
place
to buy them the story you told of the
farmer
who sprayed the crop and they didn't buy
it like these are such high quality
project
products that's why they're so expensive
first of all that means the farmer
didn't get paid
like these are not ethical products
if doterra bought that and then said
okay we're going to work with the
farmers so that it's more organic
and more and we're just not going to use
that one that might have been a
feel-good story
but no because they don't own the farms
they're not taking the risk
there's a freaking
and of course that like
oh our first world problem spraying
spraying crops then we can't have it on
our poor little our poor little first
world skin
and ingest it no i don't i do want to
make sure that my essential oils are
organic doterra is not even organic
because they know that they would get
sued for that
they're not they don't care about the
farmers they don't care about your
health
what they care about is making money
that is very clear in their pyramid
structure
in the math that is all about you
feeding off of
the 3 000 people under you their money
their connections what they buy
you can't make a living just selling
them you have to sign people up for the
for the business that isn't even a
business
because at any point and it happens time
and time again the government catches on
and says actually you can't have that
structure you can't have it seven deep
so they have to cut it off and whatever
you've built is taken away you don't get
to choose what's in
the catalog and not in the catalog they
don't have
a catalog of essential oils that is like
the top 20 only these 20 these are all
you'll ever need to have because they
need you to buy the next one so they
have to make the blends and they have to
sell you the blends
and they're making it so you have to buy
it
because they're not there for your
health they're there for their bottom
line
their money and they're living off of
all of the free labor of everyone else
do not buy from an owl do not please
leave the mlm
do not convince other people to sign up
for the mlm
whoever else is watching this do not buy
from an mlm pass
this video or the broken math video on
to your friends and family who are
asking you to come to mlm things
maybe i should have walked out as soon
as i knew that it was an mlm
but again i want to support you i want
to support everything you're doing if
you start an actual business
even if i'm anti-capitalistic which we
know i am i will support your small
business your
actual small business i will pass on all
the things for your world-changing
product
project we can brainstorm and come up
with a solution raising
for how we get ubi how we figure out how
to get our needs met
because the world isn't doing it and
we're here to make powerful things but
mlms are not the answer
that is my feedback take it for what it
is